Smith, Margaret Earhart Records 5731
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Margaret Earhart Smith Records
1941-1952
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Smith, Margaret Earhart
5731
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
5697004
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 03, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 28, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Smith, Margaret Earhart.
5697004
- A-79 Smith. U.E., 1946-1950 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- National CIO Community Services Committee, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- A-79 Smith, W.E., 1941-1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- A-79 Smith, U.E., 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ALES Conference Reports 1943-1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- W - E - Universities (Wave), 1945 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Mis. W.E. Material Clippings Removed, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- American Laborers want a Labor Extension Service, 1944-1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- A-79 Smith, W.E. Workers Ed. - University, 1946-1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- American Education Service Conference Special Service Attended 1944-1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cornell, 1948-1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)